The Amphibian Festival in Cologne
Hi from the Amphibian Festival here in Cologne.
I've been here for the last two days.
I've been part of the team of hosts announcing the bands.
and it's been so much fun.
But I'm going to show you all of it and take you along.
Have fun here at the Amphly and see you next year.
Rumors remind me of home
And you remember a smile for a while
And I meet the foreign hero
Spreading rumors that is wrong
So question guys, how long are you going to the Amphib Festival already?
10 years. 10 years Amphib Festival?
Since 2009. Since 2009. And you?
It's my second time. Your second time?
So you've been coming back all year?
Such a great festival.
It's so familiar.
That's why.
One time this year.
One time everyone meets up here.
I love the cut of this coat.
It's really cool and it's really nice.
It fits really well.
Nice!
I'm sitting for a bit.
I have the great pleasure of announcing the last band on the stage today.
And now I wish you a lot of fun.
The band comes silent!
I have a question for you. Do you actually sweat and are you always that big?
Yes and yes.
I'm on board of this ship, the third ship.
The stage of the AFI festival is really cool here, it's really hot and behind me is the famous cathedral of Palau.
I know the dark will last again.
Find a way out now
On your life depends
Like raindrops from dark clouds
To your feet beneath the ground
I know time will always pass
And this time the dark will end
Take my hand and don't let go
It's only death
I hear the words within
Your face expressions are the pain that you must feel
Unlike the rain, I want to wash away the sin
There's something inside me that calls you when it's calling you
I hear the words within
Your face expressions are a pain that you must feel
Unlike the rain, I want to wash away the sin
There's something inside me that calls you when it's calling you
Tonight
Over the mountain
We'll come
When the water's up to ice
Into the oceans
We run
With our hands held up to the skies
I'm back at the hotel after two wonderful days at the Amphifestival here in Cologne.
I love this festival every year when I'm here.
This is so cool in this city and you have this unique location.
This year it was especially unique for me
because I was able to do the hosting part with my co-announcers
and it was awesome thanks for having me Amphi, thanks for taking care of me too
Marc, Jens and Olli I hope you enjoyed this video and I hope to see you next
year here at the festival and I will see you in the next video bye oh by the way
I bought a new jacket like half an hour before the festival ended it's really
poppy and fluffy and it's just so cozy. I love it!
Have I told you what I really think?
Oh, I bet now you can see the link
Between the words that come out of your mouth
And the point you seem to care about
It needs much more than just a pretty face
To open doors with just a case